Y'all need a pilot?
Flight Risk is a action, thriller film directed by Mel Gibson.
A pilot transports a U.S.
Marshal accompanying a government witness to a trial in New York.
As they cross the Alaskan wilderness, tensions soar and trust is
tested, as not everyone on board is who they seem.
Daryl Booth, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Madolyn Harris, played by Michelle Dockery.
Winston, played by Topher Grace.
Van Sant (voice), played by Leah Remini.
Hassan (voice), played by Maaz Ali.
Coleridge (voice), played by Paul Ben-Victor.
Flight Risk is a 2025 American action thriller film directed by Mel Gibson,
and starring Mark Wahlberg, Michelle Dockery, and Topher Grace.
Its plot follows a pilot (Wahlberg) transporting a Deputy U.S.
Marshal (Dockery) and a fugitive (Grace) across the Alaskan wilderness, where the
identities and intentions of those on board come into question.
Flight Risk was released in the United States by Lionsgate on January 24, 2025.
The film received mostly negative reviews from critics
and grossed $48.7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of pilot, u.s. marshal,
fugitive, airplane accident, anchorage, alaska.
The tone is intense.